<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on taavi.wtf</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/</link><description>Recent content in Home on taavi.wtf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://taavi.wtf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google Code-In 2019</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/posts/gci-2019-20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://taavi.wtf/posts/gci-2019-20/</guid><description>I participated in Google Code-In for the first time this winter. Looks like other people are starting to blog about so here&amp;rsquo;s my blog post so I do not look like a weird antisocial hermit. To be honest, I had a lot of fun participating. In the end, I completed 31 tasks and had done little under 4.5% of all completed Wikimedia tasks.</description></item><item><title>dn42</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/dn42/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://taavi.wtf/dn42/</guid><description>I am connected to the dn42 network, which is basically a playground for BGP and other large-scale networking techniques.
Network My primary ASN is AS4242423270. I use bird2 for BGP.
My IP space is:
TAAVI-NET-V4-1: 172.22.130.128/27 TAAVI-NET-V6-1: fd96:70f6:b174::/48 Domains and DNS In addition to reverse DNS for my IP space, I control the following domains:
taavi.dn42 as4242423270.dn42 The authoritative name server for all zones is ns01.taavi.dn42 which is running bind9.</description></item><item><title>Licensing information</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/licensing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://taavi.wtf/licensing/</guid><description>Unless otherwise noted, content of this website is available under the Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International license. The source code of the theme used to create this website is available on GitHub and licensed under the MIT License.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://taavi.wtf/projects/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Uses</title><link>https://taavi.wtf/uses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://taavi.wtf/uses/</guid><description>aka: My preferred tech stack.
OS Debian for most things Windows for gaming, learning AD and some other things Essential software i3 window manager, rofi for launching programs. i3-gaps isn&amp;rsquo;t packaged for Debian currently, and I&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to build it myself. Terminator for doing terminal things. Zsh as a shell, tmux for doing many terminal things at once. Bash and Python for scripting. Font: A custom build of Iosevka (that you are reading right now)!</description></item></channel></rss>